{"deck": {"baseQ": "What country has the capital city of ", "category": "Geography", "Title": "Countries of the World"}, "0": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Capital City", "answer": "Country"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "1": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Kabul", "answer": "Afghanistan"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "2": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Tirana (Tirane)", "answer": "Albania"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "3": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Algiers", "answer": "Algeria"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "4": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Andorra la Vella", "answer": "Andorra"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "5": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Luanda", "answer": "Angola"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "6": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Saint John's", "answer": "Antigua and Barbuda"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "7": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Buenos Aires", "answer": "Argentina"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "8": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Yerevan", "answer": "Armenia"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "9": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Canberra", "answer": "Australia"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "10": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Vienna", "answer": "Austria"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "11": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Baku", "answer": "Azerbaijan"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "12": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Nassau", "answer": "Bahamas"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "13": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Manama", "answer": "Bahrain"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "14": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Dhaka", "answer": "Bangladesh"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "15": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Bridgetown", "answer": "Barbados"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "16": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Minsk", "answer": "Belarus"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "17": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Brussels", "answer": "Belgium"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "18": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Belmopan", "answer": "Belize"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "19": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Porto Novo", "answer": "Benin"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "20": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Thimphu", "answer": "Bhutan"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "21": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "La Paz (administrative), Sucre (official)", "answer": "Bolivia"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "22": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Sarajevo", "answer": "Bosnia and Herzegovina"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "23": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Gaborone", "answer": "Botswana"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "24": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Brasilia", "answer": "Brazil"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "25": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Bandar Seri Begawan", "answer": "Brunei"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "26": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Sofia", "answer": "Bulgaria"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "27": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Ouagadougou", "answer": "Burkina Faso"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "28": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Gitega", "answer": "Burundi"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "29": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Phnom Penh", "answer": "Cambodia"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "30": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Yaounde", "answer": "Cameroon"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "31": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Ottawa", "answer": "Canada"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "32": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Praia", "answer": "Cape Verde"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "33": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Bangui", "answer": "Central African Republic"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "34": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "N'Djamena", "answer": "Chad"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "35": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Santiago", "answer": "Chile"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "36": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Beijing", "answer": "China"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "37": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Bogota", "answer": "Colombia"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "38": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Moroni", "answer": "Comoros"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "39": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Kinshasa", "answer": "Congo, Democratic Republic of the"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "40": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Brazzaville", "answer": "Congo, Republic of the"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "41": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "San Jose", "answer": "Costa Rica"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "42": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Yamoussoukro", "answer": "C\u00ef\u00bf\u00bdte d'Ivoire (Ivory Coast)"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "43": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Zagreb", "answer": "Croatia"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "44": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Havana", "answer": "Cuba"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "45": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Nicosia", "answer": "Cyprus"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "46": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Prague", "answer": "Czech Republic (Czechia)"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "47": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Copenhagen", "answer": "Denmark"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "48": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Djibouti", "answer": "Djibouti"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "49": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Roseau", "answer": "Dominica"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "50": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Santo Domingo", "answer": "Dominican Republic"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "51": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Dili", "answer": "East Timor"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "52": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Quito", "answer": "Ecuador"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "53": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Cairo", "answer": "Egypt"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "54": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "San Salvador", "answer": "El Salvador"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "55": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "London", "answer": "England"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "56": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Malabo", "answer": "Equatorial Guinea"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "57": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Asmara", "answer": "Eritrea"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "58": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Tallinn", "answer": "Estonia"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "59": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Mbabana", "answer": "Eswatini (Swaziland)"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "60": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Addis Ababa", "answer": "Ethiopia"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "61": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Palikir", "answer": "Federated States of Micronesia"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "62": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Suva", "answer": "Fiji"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "63": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Helsinki", "answer": "Finland"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "64": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Paris", "answer": "France"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "65": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Libreville", "answer": "Gabon"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "66": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Banjul", "answer": "Gambia"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "67": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Tbilisi", "answer": "Georgia"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "68": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Berlin", "answer": "Germany"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "69": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Accra", "answer": "Ghana"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "70": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Athens", "answer": "Greece"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "71": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Saint George's", "answer": "Grenada"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "72": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Guatemala City", "answer": "Guatemala"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "73": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Conakry", "answer": "Guinea"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "74": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Bissau", "answer": "Guinea-Bissau"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "75": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Georgetown", "answer": "Guyana"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "76": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Port au Prince", "answer": "Haiti"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "77": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Tegucigalpa", "answer": "Honduras"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "78": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Budapest", "answer": "Hungary"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "79": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Reykjavik", "answer": "Iceland"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "80": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "New Delhi", "answer": "India"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "81": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Jakarta", "answer": "Indonesia"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "82": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Tehran", "answer": "Iran"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "83": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Baghdad", "answer": "Iraq"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "84": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Dublin", "answer": "Ireland"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "85": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Jerusalem\u00ef\u00bf\u00bd(very limited international recognition)", "answer": "Israel"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "86": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Rome", "answer": "Italy"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "87": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Kingston", "answer": "Jamaica"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "88": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Tokyo", "answer": "Japan"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "89": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Amman", "answer": "Jordan"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "90": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Nur-Sultan", "answer": "Kazakhstan"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "91": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Nairobi", "answer": "Kenya"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "92": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Tarawa Atoll", "answer": "Kiribati"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "93": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Pristina", "answer": "Kosovo"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "94": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Kuwait City", "answer": "Kuwait"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "95": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Bishkek", "answer": "Kyrgyzstan"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "96": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Vientiane", "answer": "Laos"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "97": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Riga", "answer": "Latvia"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "98": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Beirut", "answer": "Lebanon"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "99": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Maseru", "answer": "Lesotho"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "100": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Monrovia", "answer": "Liberia"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "101": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Tripoli", "answer": "Libya"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "102": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Vaduz", "answer": "Liechtenstein"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "103": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Vilnius", "answer": "Lithuania"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "104": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Luxembourg", "answer": "Luxembourg"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "105": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Antananarivo", "answer": "Madagascar"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "106": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Lilongwe", "answer": "Malawi"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "107": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Kuala Lumpur", "answer": "Malaysia"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "108": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Male", "answer": "Maldives"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "109": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Bamako", "answer": "Mali"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "110": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Valletta", "answer": "Malta"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "111": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Majuro", "answer": "Marshall Islands"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "112": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Nouakchott", "answer": "Mauritania"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "113": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Port Louis", "answer": "Mauritius"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "114": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Mexico City", "answer": "Mexico"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "115": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Chisinau", "answer": "Moldova"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "116": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Monaco", "answer": "Monaco"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "117": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Ulaanbaatar", "answer": "Mongolia"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "118": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Podgorica", "answer": "Montenegro"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "119": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Rabat", "answer": "Morocco"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "120": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Maputo", "answer": "Mozambique"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "121": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Nay Pyi Taw", "answer": "Myanmar (Burma)"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "122": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Windhoek", "answer": "Namibia"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "123": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "No official capital", "answer": "Nauru"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "124": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Kathmandu", "answer": "Nepal"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "125": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Amsterdam", "answer": "Netherlands"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "126": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Wellington", "answer": "New Zealand"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "127": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Managua", "answer": "Nicaragua"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "128": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Niamey", "answer": "Niger"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "129": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Abuja", "answer": "Nigeria"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "130": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Pyongyang", "answer": "North Korea"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "131": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Skopje", "answer": "North Macedonia (Macedonia)"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "132": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Belfast", "answer": "Northern Ireland"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "133": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Oslo", "answer": "Norway"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "134": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Muscat", "answer": "Oman"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "135": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Islamabad", "answer": "Pakistan"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "136": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Melekeok", "answer": "Palau"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "137": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Panama City", "answer": "Panama"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "138": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Port Moresby", "answer": "Papua New Guinea"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "139": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Asuncion", "answer": "Paraguay"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "140": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Lima", "answer": "Peru"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "141": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Manila", "answer": "Philippines"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "142": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Warsaw", "answer": "Poland"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "143": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Lisbon", "answer": "Portugal"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "144": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Doha", "answer": "Qatar"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "145": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Bucharest", "answer": "Romania"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "146": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Moscow", "answer": "Russia"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "147": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Kigali", "answer": "Rwanda"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "148": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Basseterre", "answer": "Saint Kitts and Nevis"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "149": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Castries", "answer": "Saint Lucia"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "150": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Kingstown", "answer": "Saint Vincent and the Grenadines"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "151": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Apia", "answer": "Samoa"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "152": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "San Marino", "answer": "San Marino"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "153": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Sao Tome", "answer": "Sao Tome and Principe"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "154": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Riyadh", "answer": "Saudi Arabia"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "155": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Edinburgh", "answer": "Scotland"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "156": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Dakar", "answer": "Senegal"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "157": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Belgrade", "answer": "Serbia"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "158": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Victoria", "answer": "Seychelles"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "159": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Freetown", "answer": "Sierra Leone"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "160": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Singapore", "answer": "Singapore"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "161": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Bratislava", "answer": "Slovakia"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "162": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Ljubljana", "answer": "Slovenia"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "163": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Honiara", "answer": "Solomon Islands"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "164": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Mogadishu", "answer": "Somalia"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "165": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Pretoria, Bloemfontein, Cape Town", "answer": "South Africa"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "166": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Seoul", "answer": "South Korea"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "167": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Juba", "answer": "South Sudan"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "168": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Madrid", "answer": "Spain"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "169": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Colombo", "answer": "Sri Lanka"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "170": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Khartoum", "answer": "Sudan"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "171": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Paramaribo", "answer": "Suriname"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "172": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Stockholm", "answer": "Sweden"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "173": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Bern", "answer": "Switzerland"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "174": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Damascus", "answer": "Syria"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "175": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Taipei", "answer": "Taiwan"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "176": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Dushanbe", "answer": "Tajikistan"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "177": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Dodoma", "answer": "Tanzania"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "178": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Bangkok", "answer": "Thailand"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "179": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Lome", "answer": "Togo"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "180": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Nuku'alofa", "answer": "Tonga"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "181": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Port of Spain", "answer": "Trinidad and Tobago"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "182": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Tunis", "answer": "Tunisia"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "183": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Ankara", "answer": "Turkey"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "184": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Ashgabat", "answer": "Turkmenistan"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "185": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Funafuti", "answer": "Tuvalu"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "186": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Kampala", "answer": "Uganda"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "187": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Kiev", "answer": "Ukraine"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "188": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Abu Dhabi", "answer": "United Arab Emirates"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "189": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "London", "answer": "United Kingdom"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "190": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Washington D.C.", "answer": "United States"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "191": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Montevideo", "answer": "Uruguay"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "192": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Tashkent", "answer": "Uzbekistan"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "193": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Port Vila", "answer": "Vanuatu"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "194": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Vatican City", "answer": "Vatican City"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "195": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Caracas", "answer": "Venezuela"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "196": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Hanoi", "answer": "Vietnam"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "197": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Cardiff", "answer": "Wales"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "198": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Sana'a", "answer": "Yemen"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "199": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Lusaka", "answer": "Zambia"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}, "200": {"card": {"type": "multi", "question": "Harare", "answer": "Zimbabwe"}, "history": {"created": 1597827504}}}